COVID-19 Pandemic Collection MS269
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Web crawls, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000182; 365 Web sites
  - Tufts CS COVID-19 Career Resources, 2020-08-14 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000474; Department of Computer Science; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts CS COVID-19 Resources, 2020-08-14 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000475; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University awards COVID-19 emergency response grants to local non-profits, 2020-08-14 -- 2020-09-18; MS269.000476; Mirage News; 1 Web sites
  - A Student Compact for Safety, 2020-08-24; MS269.000477; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - College graduates, high income earners most likely to feel helped by government during pandemic, 2020-08-24; MS269.000478; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Compliance Is Key to Successful Campus Opening, University Leaders Say, 2020-08-24; MS269.000479; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - For Undergraduates, a Smooth Test Run, 2020-08-24; MS269.000480; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - New Microscopes Help Students Learn Safely, 2020-08-24; MS269.000481; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - TUSM Student COVID Compact, 2020-08-31; MS269.000482; 1 Web sites
  - Admissions programming moves online for fall semester, virtual campus tours, 2020-09-16; MS269.000483; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Arts-related departments adapt to COVID-19 restrictions, 2020-09-16; MS269.000484; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - At Tufts Dental School, almost 200 affected by layoffs, furloughs, salary reductions, 2020-09-16; MS269.000485; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Broad Institute Processing COVID Test Results for More Than 100 Colleges, 2020-09-16; MS269.000486; NBC Boston; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts must consider local residents' concerns in proceeding with fall plans, 2020-09-16; MS269.000487; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Welcome back, Tufts, 2020-09-16; MS269.000488; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Letter from the Managing Board: Let's get to work, 2020-09-16; MS269.000489; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Majority of undergraduate students plan to return to campus this fall, 2020-09-16; MS269.000490; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - News roundup: Headlines of the summer, 2020-09-16; MS269.000491; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: An open letter to the Tufts community concerning student mental health, 2020-09-16; MS269.000492; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Q&A: Julie Ross, CMHS director, says self-care is more important now than ever, 2020-09-16; MS269.000493; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Students report long lines, wait times at Tufts Dining locations, 2020-09-16; MS269.000494; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Talloires Network awards competitive grants to global partners, 2020-09-16; MS269.000495; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Farming Project Joins COVID-19 Food Insecurity Effort, 2020-09-16; MS269.000496; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts waives eight-semester residency requirement for fall 2020 undergraduates, 2020-09-16; MS269.000497; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - 4 major leagues return to sports in the age of the pandemic, 2020-09-18; MS269.000498; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Vaccine Candidate Prevents Severe Clinical Disease in Animals, 2020-09-18; MS269.000499; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Remote students must continue to be supported as they navigate academic, social challenges, 2020-09-18; MS269.000500; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Professor Malcolm Turvey keeps film department from yelling 'cut', 2020-09-18; MS269.000501; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - The Turf Monster: A fan's perspective on sports during a pandemic, 2020-09-18; MS269.000502; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Is Studying a Pilot COVID-19 Test That Could Help Neighboring Schools, 2020-09-18; MS269.000503; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - A playlist to ease your quarantine woes, 2020-09-21; MS269.000504; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Beginner Mentality: Thank you, friends, 2020-09-21; MS269.000505; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Books to read while you self-quarantine, 2020-09-21; MS269.000506; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 protection, but make it fashion, 2020-09-21; MS269.000507; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Fitness, recreation to be restricted on campus, 2020-09-21; MS269.000508; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - From the Arts Editors: Our quarantine consumption, 2020-09-21; MS269.000509; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Jen O'Malley Dillon keeps the Biden campaign human during COVID-19, 2020-09-21; MS269.000510; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Love It Or Haute It: Hair accessories, 2020-09-21; MS269.000511; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Love It Or Haute It: Quarantine style, 2020-09-21; MS269.000512; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Take care: 10 films to watch while social distancing, 2020-09-21; MS269.000513; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Take Care: How to work and learn from home, 2020-09-21; MS269.000514; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts experiencing lower than expected COVID-19 infections, 2020-09-21; MS269.000515; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Welcome back, 2020-09-21; MS269.000516; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - 5 Tips for Home Learning, 2020-09-25; MS269.000517; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - BREAKING: Hodgdon closes after worker's close contact with individual who tested positive for COVID-19, reopening today, 2020-09-25; MS269.000518; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - College Quarantine Breakdowns Leave Some at Risk, 2020-09-25; MS269.000519; The New York Times; 1 Web sites
  - Colleges Hope Student Culture Of Coronavirus Safety Helps Keep Cases Down, 2020-09-25; MS269.000520; WBUR; 1 Web sites
  - Coming to Campus: Onboard Testing & Arrival Quarantine for AS&E Students, 2020-09-25; MS269.000521; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Testing Lab Shows How Colleges Can Reopen Safely, 2020-09-25; MS269.000522; Scientific American; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 thrusts college presidents into the hot seat, 2020-09-25; MS269.000523; The Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - Does Working from Home Actually Work?, 2020-09-25; MS269.000524; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - For remote first-years, a different start to college, 2020-09-25; MS269.000525; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - How to Tell the Flu from COVID-19, 2020-09-25; MS269.000526; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Do you hear the people sing (and play wind instruments)?, 2020-09-25; MS269.000527; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - The Quest for Justice: Improving Health, 2020-09-25; MS269.000528; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Dining workers strained by COVID-19 impact, understaffed, 2020-09-25; MS269.000529; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Fall 2020 Onboard COVID-19 Testing Procedure, 2020-09-25; MS269.000530; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Alumni Spearhead COVID-19 Responses, 2020-10-01; MS269.000531; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Boston Mayor Marty Walsh, city officials join Tisch College to discuss COVID-19, racial inequities, 2020-10-01; MS269.000532; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - How COVID-19 Has Affected Special Education Students, 2020-10-01; MS269.000533; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Keep the Cameras Rolling: A post-COVID world, 2020-10-01; MS269.000534; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Monaco, administrators address COVID-19 concerns, spring plans in virtual town hall, 2020-10-01; MS269.000535; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Student organizations and the Tufts administration must be more inclusive of remote international students, 2020-10-01; MS269.000536; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Philosophy in Focus: Should we be here?, 2020-10-01; MS269.000537; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Professors, students react to adjusted lab courses, COVID-19 impact on STEM, 2020-10-01; MS269.000538; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - 2020 $100k Jean Mayer Prize from Tufts Nutrition awarded for tackling COVID-19 food crisis, 2020-10-05; MS269.000539; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Another Look at Fall Academics at the School of Arts and Sciences and SMFA at Tufts, 2020-10-05; MS269.000540; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Community, strength, endurance on Tufts Marathon Team, 2020-10-05; MS269.000541; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts Dining workers deserve better, 2020-10-05; MS269.000542; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts, prioritize community among first-year and transfer students, 2020-10-05; MS269.000543; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Engineering Success in the Virtual Classroom, 2020-10-05; MS269.000544; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Hitting the Reset Button on Intro to Engineering, 2020-10-05; MS269.000545; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Student performance groups move forward despite COVID-19 obstacles, 2020-10-05; MS269.000546; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts announces new Thanksgiving policy, will not allow students who travel for the break to return, 2020-10-05; MS269.000547; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Coronavirus Archives - International Center, 2020 -- 2020; MS269.000548; International Center; 1 Web sites
    Frequency: one-time crawl.
  - Tufts Community Response Volunteer Groups, 2020 -- 2021; MS269.000549; Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life; 1 Web sites
    Frequency: monthly crawl.
  - College communities rally together to support students struggling with campus departures, 2021 February 19; MS269.000550; NPR Marketplace; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University President Anthony Monaco on Preparing to House COVID-19 Patients, 2021 February 19; MS269.000551; WGBH; 1 Web sites
  - Community Testing Program, 2020 -- 2021; MS269.000552; Tufts Community Relations; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Taps Olive's AI Centers to Expand COVID-19 Testing, 2020 October 14; MS269.000553; HIT Infrastructure; 1 Web sites
  - How Does COVID-19 Create Inequity in K-12 Education?, 2020 October 14; MS269.000554; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - A Push to Prevent the Next Pandemic, 2020 October 14; MS269.000555; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Biologists Find Virtual Ways to Study the Outdoors, 2020 October 14; MS269.000556; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University to provide free COVID-19 testing for abutters, 2020 October 14; MS269.000557; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University sees low case count, rolls out neighborhood testing plan in Somerville, Medford, 2020 October 14; MS269.000558; Wicked Local Somerville; 1 Web sites
  - Tuff Talks: Love in COVID times, 2020 October 14; MS269.000559; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Who returns, who gets tested? New England schools differ in COVID-19 response, 2020 October 14; MS269.000560; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Too early to determine compliance with state flu shot requirement, university officials say, 2020 October 14; MS269.000561; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - BREAKING: Spring semester to begin Feb. 1, spring break to be shortened, 2020 October 14; MS269.000562; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Confusion surrounds residential cohorts, enforcement of system, residential assistants say, 2020 October 14; MS269.000563; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts launches new pooled testing study to help K-12 schools, 2020 October 14; MS269.000564; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts suspends almost all study abroad programs for spring 2021, 2020 October 14; MS269.000565; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Michael Jordan contributes as university infection control health director, leads Tufts' response to pandemic, 2020 October 14; MS269.000566; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts to test Medford, Somerville neighbors for COVID-19 free of cost, 2020 October 14; MS269.000567; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - The Countdown: What we can learn from Trump's diagnosis, 2020 October 14; MS269.000568; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Sobremesa: Falling through the cracks of COVID-19, 2020 October 14; MS269.000569; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Flu vaccinations are crucial during a pandemic, 2020 October 14; MS269.000570; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - NESCAC cancels winter sports season amid safety concerns, 2020 October 14; MS269.000571; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Olive's AI Workforce to Revolutionize COVID-19 Testing at Tufts Medical Center, 2020 October 14; MS269.000572; PR Newswire; 1 Web sites
  - A Lab With All the Comforts of Home—Because It Is, 2020 October 23; MS269.000573; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Unsure About Taking Your Child to the Physician or Dentist? Don't Be, Providers Say, 2020 October 23; MS269.000574; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Mass. requires flu vaccinations for college students, Tufts urges quick compliance, 2020 October 23; MS269.000575; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts to lead 5-year research program on zoonotic disease spillover, 2020 October 23; MS269.000576; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Parents Weekend adopts virtual format with live webinar, 2020 October 23; MS269.000577; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Senate appoints new members to Allocations Board, discusses Tufts SJP's resolution, 2020 October 23; MS269.000578; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Career Center adapts career fairs to online format, maintains student engagement, 2020 October 23; MS269.000579; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Somerville sees rise in COVID-19 cases, enters red category, 2020 October 23; MS269.000580; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Senate assigns committee placements, discusses online transition of Senate activities, 2020 October 23; MS269.000581; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts sets standard for containing the spread of COVID-19, 2020 October 23; MS269.000582; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Adjust spring plans to prioritize student mental health, 2020 October 23; MS269.000583; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts should better enforce residential cohort system, 2020 October 23; MS269.000584; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Updates from GSBS, 2020 -- 2021; MS269.000585; Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Communications and Guidance, 2020 -- 2021; MS269.000586; School of Medicine; 1 Web sites
  - Coaches Step Up to the Plate for Quarantining Students, 2020 October 30; MS269.000587; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University, Medford and Somerville launch innovative COVID-19 testing program for PK-12 schools, 2020 October 30; MS269.000588; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Cartoon: Get your darn flu shot, 2020 October 30; MS269.000589; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts organizes flu clinics with CVS Pharmacy, 2020 October 30; MS269.000590; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Senate discusses general election, Thanksgiving break, 2020 October 30; MS269.000591; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts to allow practice of singing, wind instruments in Mods, 2020 October 30; MS269.000592; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Admissions extends early decision deadline, 2020 October 30; MS269.000593; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: As winter approaches, provide students with safe options to socialize, 2020 October 30; MS269.000594; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Applying to a Tufts graduate school? Here's what to expect, 2020 November 02; MS269.000595; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Students, professors adjust to remote exams, 2020 November 02; MS269.000596; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Religious communities persevere, innovate in wake of pandemic restriction, 2020 November 02; MS269.000597; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - A Positive Approach to Health and Safety Amid COVID-19, 2020 November 06; MS269.000598; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Keep the Cameras Rolling: 'Midsommar' and isolation, 2020 November 06; MS269.000599; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts announces 10 p.m. COVID-19 curfew, 2020 November 06; MS269.000600; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Extend Exceptional Pass policies to spring 2021, 2020 November 06; MS269.000601; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Philosophy in Focus: No, I will not agree to disagree, 2020 November 06; MS269.000602; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Novel pool testing for coronavirus seen as potential K-12 model, 2020 -- 2020; MS269.000603; Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts issues travel restrictions, academic precautions in response to coronavirus, 2020 December 01; MS269.000604; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Health Service tightens COVID-19 testing procedure, 2020 December 01; MS269.000605; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Higher number of students expected to return to campus for spring semester, 2020 December 01; MS269.000606; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Clinical and Translational Science Institute (CTSI) Announces COVID-19 Pilot Studies Grant Recipients, 2020 December 17; MS269.000607; Center for Leading Innovation and Collaboration; 1 Web sites
  - Alumnus Donates 1 Million Masks to Tufts, 2020 December 17; MS269.000608; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts' Fall Festival of Plays Reinvents Theater for the Pandemic, 2020 December 17; MS269.000609; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - The Coronavirus Sneaks Its Way Into Cells. But How?, 2020 December 17; MS269.000610; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Face Masks Pose a Health Risk to Animals, 2020 December 17; MS269.000611; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Four Things Experts Have Learned From the Pandemic, 2020 December 17; MS269.000612; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Holiday Meal for 1,800? Sure, No Problem, 2020 December 17; MS269.000613; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Something Wrong With Your Sniffer? It Could Be the Coronavirus, 2020 December 17; MS269.000614; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Staying Home in COVID-19 Means Higher Electricity Bills, 2020 December 17; MS269.000615; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Summer Projects Allow Students to Combat COVID-19, Racial Injustice, 2020 December 17; MS269.000616; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - WHO Chief Scientist, NEJM Editor Headline Tufts COVID-19 Symposium, 2020 December 17; MS269.000617; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 forces fast fashion to slow down, 2020 December 17; MS269.000618; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Sobremesa: The importance of equitable vaccination distribution, 2020 December 17; MS269.000619; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - In-person students miss animal interaction, 2020 December 17; MS269.000620; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Navigating Fall Break: Students weigh whether to stay on campus, university shares decision-making process, 2020 December 17; MS269.000621; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Fall Festival of Plays adapts to COVID-19, addresses themes of race, inequality, 2020 December 17; MS269.000622; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Class of 2020 shares difficulties with post-graduation job search, 2020 December 17; MS269.000623; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Reflections on first semester: First-years talk about college experience, 2020 December 17; MS269.000624; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - How to enjoy art during the pandemic, 2020 December 17; MS269.000625; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Professor Eitan Hersh invites grandparents of students to attend course virtually, 2020 December 17; MS269.000626; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Campus sees spike in waste due to COVID-19 guidelines, takeout dining, 2020 December 17; MS269.000627; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Students report noncompliance with university guidelines amid COVID-19 surge, 2020 December 17; MS269.000628; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Fletcher students cover pandemic's effect on global affairs in 'TwentyTwenty' podcast, 2020 December 17; MS269.000629; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Medical school, Cummings school professors research viral proteins, COVID-19 infection, 2020 December 17; MS269.000630; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts sees decrease in mental health-related calls during COVID-19 pandemic, 2020 December 17; MS269.000631; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Sufficient supply of COVID-19 materials available through spring as Tufts continues to support host communities, 2020 December 17; MS269.000632; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Cummings Center construction delayed by pandemic, completion now set for October 2021, 2020 December 17; MS269.000633; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Office of the Provost hosts virtual program on anti-Asian racism, COVID-19 impact, 2020 December 17; MS269.000634; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Why I am volunteering to give myself COVID-19, 2020 December 17; MS269.000635; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts, accommodate students who cannot return home for winter break, 2020 December 17; MS269.000636; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Students must continue to follow COVID-19 guidelines as cases rise, 2020 December 17; MS269.000637; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts, here are some New Year's resolutions, 2020 December 17; MS269.000638; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts professors should continue empathetic approach to teaching as semester comes to a close, 2020 December 17; MS269.000639; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts suspends athletic practices through the calendar year to combat rising COVID-19 cases, 2020 December 17; MS269.000640; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts COVID-19 Research Symposium, 2020 -- 2020; MS269.000641; Office of the Vice Provost for Research; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University to provide free COVID-19 testing for abutters, 2020 December 17; MS269.000642; City of Medford, Massachusetts; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Student Diagnosed With Coronavirus, 2020 December 17; MS269.000643; NBC Boston; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University, Medford and Somerville Launch Innovative COVID-19 Testing Program for PK-12 Schools, 2020 December 17; MS269.000644; City of Somerville, Massachusetts; 1 Web sites
  - Three test positive for COVID-19 while Tufts students flow onto campus, 2020 December 17; MS269.000645; The Somerville Times; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts updates quarantine duration protocol in accordance with new Massachusetts guidelines, 2020 -- 2021; MS269.000646; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Medical Center receives 2,925 doses of COVID-19 vaccine, begins to vaccinate employees, 2020 December 23; MS269.000647; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Positive COVID-19 case at Dewick incites worry, anger from workers over protocol, 2020 December 23; MS269.000648; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Baker tells residents to stay home for the holidays as vaccination of health workers get under way, 2020 December 23; MS269.000649; Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - The Pandemic and Childhood Weight Gain, 2021 January 11; MS269.000650; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Medical and Dental Students Start to Receive COVID-19 Vaccine, 2021 January 11; MS269.000651; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - In 2020, All Hands Were on Board at Tufts Responding to the Pandemic, 2021 January 27; MS269.000652; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Bringing Virtual Study Abroad to Students, 2021 January 27; MS269.000653; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Using Advances in Digital Pathology to Transform Teaching and Research, 2021 January 27; MS269.000654; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - What Happens If COVID-19 Infects Wild Animals?, 2021 January 27; MS269.000655; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - BREAKING: Tufts tightens COVID-19 restrictions on students studying in person, 2021 February 05; MS269.000656; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts begins Phase 1 vaccinations for health care workers, first responders, 2021 February 05; MS269.000657; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites